我想问你，你和卡尔文·库珀在一起，对吧?
I was gonna ask, you're with Calvin Cooper, right?
—什么?-你要和他一起去
- What? - You're traveling with him.
-他怎么样，好人?-他是个婊子。
- What's he like, nice guy? - He's a cunt.
哦,对了。是的,我的意思是,
Oh, right. Yeah, I mean,
他看起来是个好人。你知道，你只是从一些人身上得到了那种感觉。
he seems like a nice guy. You know, you just get that vibe off some people.
他是你的朋友吗?
And is he a friend of yours?
—客户端。—客户端。
- A client. - Client.
看看你。的意。
Look at you. Fancy.
是的,喜欢。我现在很帅，杰米。
Yeah, fancy. I'm fancy now, Jamie.
你需要什么吗?
Is there something you need?
嗯…
Uh...
你能给我签个名吗?
Do you think maybe you could get me a little autograph?
是给帕姆的，只是…
It's for Pam, it's just...
是的，当然，还有别的吗?因为我真的需要…
Yup, sure thing, is there something else? Because I really need to...
哦,不,好了。谢谢。你去吧。
Oh, no, great. Thanks. You go for it.